export const questions = [
	//Choice 1
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question: 'How many ribs does a normal human being have?',
				options: ['Thirty', 'Forty One', 'Forty Five', 'Twenty Four'],
				answer: 'Twenty Four'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question:
					'Tina took dinner at 8:55 p.m. she decided to go to bed 1 hr 20 min later. At what time did she go to bed?',
				options: ['10:15 pm', '10:20 pm', '10:25 pm', '10:30 pm'],
				answer: '10:15 pm'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 2
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question:
					'Which of these languages is not represented on the language panel of the Indian banknotes?',
				options: ['Bhojpuri', 'Urdu', 'Bengali', 'Tamil'],
				answer: 'Bhojpuri'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question:
					'The difference between smallest 4 digit number and largest three digit number is ______.',
				options: ['100', '0', '1', '999'],
				answer: '1'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 3
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question:
					'Vasundhara Raje  was the first Chief Minister of _______state.',
				options: ['West Bengal', 'Rajasthan', 'Maharashtra', 'Madhya Pradesh'],
				answer: 'Rajasthan'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question: 'Which instrument is Ustad Allah Rakha associated with?',
				options: ['Sitar', 'Sarangi', 'Tabla', 'Shehnai'],
				answer: 'Tabla'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 4
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question:
					'From where did Shivaji Maharaj escape by hiding inside a basket?',
				options: ['Agra', 'Lucknow', 'Sinhagad', 'Purandar'],
				answer: 'Agra'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question: '18:45 pm is equal to _________.',
				options: [
					'Quarter to 7',
					'Quarter to 6',
					'Quarter past 6',
					'Quarter past 7'
				],
				answer: 'Quarter to 7'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 5
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question: '_____________ is the author of ‘Panchtantra tales’.',
				options: [
					'Khushwant Singh',
					'Vishnu Sharma',
					'Vikram Seth',
					'Vikram Chandra'
				],
				answer: 'Vishnu Sharma'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question: 'Which of the following number is divisible by 3, 6 and 9?',
				options: ['45', '54', '63', ' 81'],
				answer: '54'
			}
		]
		
	],
	//Choice 6
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question: 'The simplest form of   1.5 : 2.5    is __________.',
				options: ['6 : 10', '15 : 25', '0.75 : 1.25', '3:5'],
				answer: '3:5'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question:
					'How many words are misspelled in the following sentence:\nThe camal carravan crossed the dessert for a weak before it arrived at the oassis.',
				options: ['3', '2', '4', '5'],
				answer: '5'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 7
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question:
					'The leaves of the ________ tree appear on the flag of the United Nations?',
				options: ['Mulberry', 'Olive', 'Cherry', 'Maple'],
				answer: 'Olive'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question: 'Penicillium is a _________.',
				options: ['Algae', 'Fungus', 'Bacteria', 'Yeast'],
				answer: 'Fungus'
			}
		]
	],
	//Choice 8
	[
		[
			{
				id: '1',
				question:
					'Which country has a tri-colour flag with white, blue and red bands?',
				options: ['Russia', 'Canada', 'China', 'Afghanistan'],
				answer: 'Russia'
			},
			{
				id: '2',
				question: 'The square root of (7 + 3√5) (7 - 3√5) is _______.',
				options: ['√5', '2', '4', '2√5'],
				answer: '2'
			}
		]
	]
	
];
